<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="74">
    <author>Achimobil</author>
    <contributor>Mannie313</contributor>
    <version>0.4.0.0_beta_1</version>
    <title>
        <en>Autoloader Transport Pack</en>
        <de>Autoloader Transport Paket</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[The Friesenjung Transport Pack known from the 19 converted to the 22.
My autoloader for pallets and bales has been integrated here.

The first version here is a pure conversion. This means that everything that the original pack did not have, this one does not have either.
This includes e.g. indicator lights inside. 
As these are LS17 models in the base, I did not get a choice of colours or working mirrors for the conversion.
It is planned to improve this with and with. If you are interested in working with me in the next months, please contact me.

It is not easy to put the autoloading capacities into text. Therefore here are only a few key data per model.
Model number => Euro pallets | round bales 125 | square bales
03 => 16 | 12 | 9 
04 => 24 | 16 | 15
05 => 30 | 22 | 18
06 => 36 | 26 | 21
07 => 42 | 32 | 24
08 => 50 | 36 | 30
Of course, the other autoloader items also fit, but that is beyond the scope of the description here.
Listing 12 tools here doesn't make much sense from my point of view.

Prices
Truck: 135000€ - 210000€
Trailer: 12000@ - 25000€

Includes the following with flatbeds and autoload:
3 Trucks
3 trailers with turntable
3 trailers with drawbar
3 trailers

Credits
Honour to whom honour is due. The Friesenjung Transport Pack was converted here.
Thank you at this point for the permission to use this as a basis.
The Friesenjung has nothing to do with the conversion itself, if something is wrong, please contact me.
The models are originally from Alfredix, so a special thanks to him for the models.

The vehicles are based on the LS17 models from Alfredix, because that was already the case in the FJ Mod.
I don't know yet if I am allowed/able to convert them to his new LS19 models, which still have to be converted to the 22.

Bugs and suggestions welcome on <a href="https://github.com/Achimobil/FS22_Transport_Pack">GitHub</a>.

This compilation of mine may only be published with the original link.
Changing and republishing only with permission.

Changelog
0.4.0.0
- changes from Mannie313 for driving backwards with Autodrive only for the trailers
- replace window dirt

0.3.0.0
- Replaced old Chasis of TGS with new Giants Chasis inkl. color choice
- Fixed Triggers in movement
 
0.2.1.0
- Drawbar trailer equipped with supports (Thanks to EWW_Bobo)
 
0.2.0.0
- Unfolding deactivated during field work
- Load quantities defined for autoloader version 1.8

0.1.2.0
- New store pictures from Cassy
- Trucks are now shown as such on the map
- Widths for AD collision detection corrected
- Translations cleaned up and store texts corrected
- Ramp usage now translated
- Truck trailer connections fixed
- Trailer connections completely redone
- Autoload trigger ranges improved
- Cornering lights and rear work lights strengthened
- Wear optics decreased
]]></en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Das aus dem 19er bekannte Friesenjung Transport Pack konvertiert in den 22er.
Mein Autoloader für Paletten und Ballen wurde hier integriert.

Die erste Version ist hier eine reine Konvertierung. Das heißt alles das, was das ursprüngliche Packet nicht hatte, hat auch dieses hier noch nicht.
Dazu zählen z.B. Blinker Lampen im inneren. 
Da es sich um LS17 Modelle in der Basis handelt habe ich bei der Konvertierung keine Farbwahl und keine funktionierenden Spiegel hin bekommen.
Es ist geplant dies mit und mit noch zu verbessern. Wer Interesse hat, mit mir in den nächsten Monaten daran zu Arbeiten kann sich gerne bei mir melden.

Die Autoloader Kapazitäten in Text zu fassen ist nicht übersichtlich hin zu bekommen. Deshalb hier nur ein paar Eckdaten dazu pro Model.
Modelnummer => Europaletten | Rundballen 125 | Quaderballen
03 => 16 | 12 | 9 
04 => 24 | 16 | 15
05 => 30 | 22 | 18
06 => 36 | 26 | 21
07 => 42 | 32 | 24
08 => 50 | 36 | 30
Natürlich passen auch die anderen Autoloader Sachen, aber das sprengt hier den Rahmen der Beschreibung.
Auch 12 Fahrzeuge hier auflisten macht nicht viel sinn aus meiner Sicht.

Preise
LKW: 135000€ - 210000€
Anhänger: 12000@ - 25000€

Enthält folgendes mit Pritschen und Autoload:
3 LKW
3 Anhänger mit Drehschemel
3 Anhänger mit Deichsel
3 Auflieger

Credits
Ehre wem Ehre gebührt. Konvertiert wurde hier das Friesenjung Transport Pack.
Danke an dieser Stelle für die Genehmigung das als Grundlage zu verwenden.
Mit der Konvertierung selbst hat der Friesenjung nichts zu tun, sollte da was nicht stimmen, dann bitte an mich wenden.
Die Modelle sind ursprünglich von Alfredix, somit gilt auch ihm hier ein besonderer Danke für die Modelle.

Die Fahrzeuge basieren auf den LS17 Modellen von Alfredix, weil das auf im FJ Mod schon so war.
Ob ich die auf seine neuen LS19 Modelle, die erst noch in den 22er Konvertiert werden müssen, umstellen darf/kann, weiß ich noch nicht.

Fehler und Anregungen gerne auf <a href="https://github.com/Achimobil/FS22_Transport_Pack">GitHub</a>

Diese Zusammenstellung von mir darf nur mit Original Link veröffentlicht werden.
Das Verändern und neu veröffentlichen nur mit Genehmigung.

Changelog
0.4.0.0
- Anpassungen von Mannie313 um mit Autodrive rückwärts zu fahren nur bei den Anhängern
- Fenster dirt erneuert

0.3.0.0
- Altes Außenchasis des TGS durch das neue von Giants ersetzt inkl. Farbwahl.
- Trigger fixiert in Bewegung

0.2.1.0
- Deichsel Anhänger mit Stützen ausgestattet (Danke an EWW_Bobo)

0.2.0.0
- Ausklappen bei Feldarbeit deaktiviert
- Lademengen definiert für Autoloader Version 1.8

0.1.2.0
- Neue Shop Bilder von Cassy
- Trucks werden auf der Karte jetzt auch als solche angezeigt
- Breiten für AD kollisionserkennung korrigiert
- Übersetzungen aufgeräumt und Shoptexte korrigiert
- Rampen Nutzung jetzt übersetzt
- Truck Anhängeranschlüsse repariert
- Anschlüsse der Auflieger komplett neu gemacht
- Autoload Triggerbereiche verbessert
- Kurvenlicht und hinteres Arbeitslicht verstärkt
- Verschleiß Optik vermindert
]]></de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>store/modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TGS03_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TGS04_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TGS05_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TGD03_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TGD04_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TGD05_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TSDH03_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TSDH04_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TSDH05_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TST06_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TST07_Pritsche.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/fj_CargoLine/CargoLine_TST08_Pritsche.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
    <dependencies>
        <dependency>FS22_aPalletAutoLoader</dependency>
    </dependencies>
    <vehicleTypes>
        <type name="fjPritscheTruck" parent="woodTruck" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="FS22_aPalletAutoLoader.aPalletAutoLoader"/>
        </type>
        <type name="fjPritscheTrailer" parent="transportTrailer" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="FS22_aPalletAutoLoader.aPalletAutoLoader"/>
        </type>
    </vehicleTypes>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="l10n"/>
</modDesc>
